## Gilberto Ferreira Prado de Souza

#### **Personal Information**

Nationality: Brazilian (born in Belo Horizonte, Minas Gerais, Brazil)

Marital status: Single

Address: Arraial Novo, 267 - Dom Bosco

Belo Horizonte MG - ZIP Code: 30850-310

Phone.: (+55) 31 993.401.808 E-Mail: obetoferreira@gmail.com

Birthdate: January 9, 1995

#### **Summary**

Brazilian, male, 21 years old.

Frontend Engineer with 5+ years experience in web development, user interface/experience and graphic design.

Living in Belo Horizonte, working at Construct App, studying Information Systems at UNA. Also active member from Google Developers Groups and passionate for development, design and technology.

## **Specialization Overview**

Operating systems Linux/Unix, MS-Windows

Languages JavaScript, PHP, HTML, CSS, Java, Markdown

Internet / Web Wordpress, Node.js, Express.js, Jekyll

Version Control Git (Github, Bitbucket)

Libraries AngularJS, JQuery, Bower, Yeoman, Gulp, Grunt, LESS, SASS

Databases MySQL

NoSQL MongoDB

Softwares Adobe Photoshop/Illustrator/Indesign, Sketch, Microsoft Office

#### **Professional Experience**

## Front-end Developer and Designer

Dec 2015 – Present

Construct App

Technologies: AngularJS, NodeJS, MongoDB, Wordpress.

Activity: Design and develop new features to the company's web-app, internal tools, blog and

website.

**Front-end Engineer** 

Jun 2014 – Dec 2015

Quartel Design

Technologies: Wordpress, LESS, JQuery

# Gilberto Ferreira Prado de Souza

**Activity:** Develop custom Wordpress themes from scratch, help to improve the company's tools and frameworks.

## Front-end Engineer and Designer (Intern)

Jan 2014 – Jun 2014

Verticis Web Studio

**Technologies:** Twitter Bootstrap, JQuery, Symfony 2

Activity: Design website layouts, branding materials and graphic media. Develop front-end

interfaces to run with PHP back-end engine as well.

Graphic Designer Dec 2012 – Dec 2013

**Guia Integrated Communication** 

**Technologies:** Adobe Illustrator/Photoshop/Indesign **Activity:** Design branding materials and graphic media.

<u>Intern</u> Jan 2011 – Dec 2012

Hetsi Web Agency

Technologies: Adobe Illustrator/Photoshop, HTML, CSS

Activity: Design branding materials and graphic media. Develop simple HTML and CSS

interfaces as well.

#### Education

Bachelor Information Systems, UNA MG, Belo Horizonte December 2018 (In progress). Technical Graphic Designer and Web Developer, Seven CG, Belo Horizonte December 2013.

#### **Technology Stack**

JavaScript 3 years
JQuery 3 years
PHP 2 years
Wordpress 2 years
AngularJS 1 year
NodeJS 1 year
MongoDB 1 year